{
  "status": "success",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "The phrase 'bonafida' means---------",
      "answer": "good faith",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["good faith", "from office", "to the end", "reminder"]
    },
    {
      "question": "prima facie' means------",
      "answer": "at first sight",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["at first sight", "definetly", "in the absence", "unfortunately"]
    },
    {
      "question": "ab initio means'----------",
      "answer": "from the beginning",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "from the beginning",
        "till the end",
        "expansion of initials",
        "NOT"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Malafide' means-------",
      "answer": "bad faith",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bad faith", "from office", "to the end", "reminder"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Facsimile' means-------",
      "answer": "exact copy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["exact copy", "dupilcate copy", "reversed", "beware"]
    },
    {
      "question": "bon voyage' means",
      "answer": "to wish good journey",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["to wish good journey", "best day", "experience", "precious"]
    },
    {
      "question": "enbloc' means-----------",
      "answer": "all together ",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["all together ", "all at same time", "sentimental", "in reality"]
    },
    {
      "question": "sine die' means----------",
      "answer": "indefinitely",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["indefinitely", "greatful", "magnitude", "definitely"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The latin word  'adhoc' means----------",
      "answer": "for the special purpose",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "for the special purpose",
        "to the end",
        "for the mean time",
        "from office"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Tittle - tattle' means-------------",
      "answer": "gossip",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["gossip", "argument", "confusion", "sudden"]
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the expression 'au fait' means:",
      "answer": "familiar or acquainted",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "familiar or acquainted",
        "actually existing but not legally",
        "in the open air",
        "Not"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The latin word 'magnum opus' means:",
      "answer": "a great work",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "a great work",
        "with bad faith",
        "with bad faith",
        "at my own risk"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct meaning of the foreign word 'vis a vis':",
      "answer": "Face to face",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "Face to face",
        "back to back",
        "side to side",
        "looking at each other"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Vice versa' means:",
      "answer": "reversed",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["reversed", "normally", "forwarded", "probably"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The toy was very attractive , but nobody knew its mode of operation",
      "answer": "modus operandi",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["modus operandi", "locus standi", "in tuto", "modus vivendi"]
    },
    {
      "question": "the meaning of 'status quo' -----------",
      "answer": "existing condition",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "existing condition",
        "ability to lead",
        "responsibility",
        "experience"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The expression 'vox populi ' ---------",
      "answer": "voice of the people",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["voice of the people", "dutoral verdict", "opinion pol", "Not"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the abbrevate of 'eg':",
      "answer": "exempli gratia",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "exempli gratia",
        "eastern egg",
        "example given",
        "existing gratia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Carpe diem' means------",
      "answer": "enjoy the present day",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "enjoy the present day",
        "unrestricted authority",
        "hated thing",
        "best day"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "choose the meaning of the Latin word 'viva voce'------",
      "answer": "orally",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["orally", "literally", "carefully", "legibly"]
    },
    {
      "question": "At the end of the speech the leader wished ---------- to all.",
      "answer": "au revoir",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["au revoir", "obita dictum", "ad valorem", "amen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The president was specially happy to vist the school because it was his;",
      "answer": "alma mater",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["alma mater", "sin die", "bona-fide", "prima facie"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The meaning of the term nota bene:",
      "answer": "note carefully",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "note carefully",
        "exceptional",
        "for good cause",
        "no need to be noted"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Circa' means--------",
      "answer": "about",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["about", "correct", "sure", "alone"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The appropriate meaning of the 'felo de se ' is --------",
      "answer": "suicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["suicide", "absent minded", "beloved", "in progress"]
    },
    {
      "question": "ad rem ",
      "answer": "correct reply",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "correct reply",
        "common languge",
        "confidential meeting",
        "open and frank"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Lingua franca",
      "answer": "common languge",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "common languge",
        "correct reply",
        "open and frank",
        "confidential meeting"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Tete a Tete",
      "answer": "confidential meeting",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "confidential meeting",
        "common languge",
        "correct reply",
        "open and frank"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "glas nost",
      "answer": "open and frank",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "open and frank",
        "confidential meeting",
        "common languge",
        "correct reply"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "carte blanche",
      "answer": "restricted power to act on one ' own",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "restricted power to act on one ' own",
        "deadlock",
        "an abrupt change of govt by force",
        "correction made in a book after printing."
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "impass",
      "answer": "deadlock",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "deadlock",
        "restricted power to act on one ' own",
        "correction made in a book after printing.",
        "an abrupt change of govt by force"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "coup d' etat",
      "answer": "an abrupt change of govt by force",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "an abrupt change of govt by force",
        "deadlock",
        "restricted power to act on one ' own",
        "correction made in a book after printing."
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "corrigendum",
      "answer": "correction made in a book after printing.",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "correction made in a book after printing.",
        "an abrupt change of govt by force",
        "deadlock",
        "restricted power to act on one ' own"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "nom de piume",
      "answer": "pen name",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "pen name",
        "correction made in a book after printing.",
        "an abrupt change of govt by force",
        "deadlock"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "nom de guerre",
      "answer": "pseudoname",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "pseudoname",
        "pen name",
        "deadlock",
        "correction made in a book after printing."
      ]
    }
  ]
}
